https://orpheusmusic.com.au/content/3-terms-and-conditions-of-use

MenuHomeSheet Music   Recorder SoloRecorder DuetsRecorder TriosRecorder QuartetsRecorder QuintetsRecorder Sextets7 and 8 Recorders9 and more RecordersChristmas Music for the RecorderRecorder + AccompanimentRecorder Collections and AnthologiesRecorder ConcertosChamber Music that includes RecorderOther Recorder Ensemble MusicRecorder TutorsRecorder Exam BooksTheory/Ear-trainingBooks that have a connection to the Recorder Recorders &
Accessories   Recorder MakersAulos RecordersKung RecordersMollenhauer RecordersPaetzold RecordersYamaha RecordersZen-on Recorders  Recorder SizesGarklein RecordersSopranino RecordersDescant RecordersTreble RecordersA-415 Hz RecordersTenor RecordersComfort Tenor RecordersBass Recorders  Recorder MaintenanceRecorder Oils Greases Recorder Cleaning BrushesRecorder Maintenance Kits  Recorder AccessoriesThumbrestsCasesStraps and Stands  Recorder Fashion Accessories Courses   Course ArchivesCourse 2020Current Courses RecordingsWaldorf SchoolsMerchandiseOn SaleResourcesAbout UsContact Us
> Terms and conditions of use WishlistNo products » My wishlistsOrpheus Music Terms and Conditions of useIntroductionOrpheus Music regards customer privacy as an important part of our relationship with our customers. The following privacy policy applies to all users of the Orpheus Music website, and conforms to Internet privacy standards Collection of InformationIf you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact Peter Biffin on 61.2.6772 2205. In order to use the Orpheus Music website, we may require information from you in order to provide the best service possible. All correspondence may also be collected and stored, particularly in regards to sales, support and accounts, including email. Use of Collected InformationAny details collected from Orpheus Music customers is required in order to provide you with our products and/or services, and a high level of customer service. We ask nothing of our customers that is not directly related to that goal Storage of Collected InformationThe security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card numbers) on our website, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). When Credit Card details are collected, we simply pass them on in order to be processed as required. We never permanently store complete Credit Card details. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and when we have received it. If you have any questions about security on our website, you can email us at info@orpheusmusic.com.au. OrdersIf you purchase a product or service from us, we may request certain personally identifiable information from you. You may be required to provide contact details (such as name, email and postal address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiry date). We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you. CommunicationsOrpheus Music uses personally identifiable information for essential communications, such as emails, accounts information, and critical service details. We may also use this information for other purposes including some promotional emails. If at any time a customer wishes not to receive such correspondence, they may request to be removed from any mailing lists by emailing us at info@orpheusmuisic.com.au. Third PartiesOrpheus Music may, at its discretion use other third parties to provide essential services on our site or for our business processes. We may share your details as necessary for the third party to be able to provide that service. These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purpose. Orpheus Music does not share any information with third parties for any unknown or unrelated uses. LegalWe reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our website. LinksLinks on the Orpheus Music site to external entities are not covered within this policy. The terms and conditions set out in this privacy statement only cover the domain name of Orpheus Music Changes to Privacy PolicyIf we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our homepage
